helpserve.com 2014-06-19

# Privacy policy - Kayako

  * [ Home](http://www.kayako.com/) »
  * Privacy

Your privacy is incredibly important to us. We wouldn't want people mistreating our information, so we'll do everything we can to safeguard yours. Any information that we collect will only be used in ways for which you have consented. 

By using Kayako websites, you agree and give consent to the terms set out here. 

This policy came into effect on the 19th March 2010, and was last updated on the 19th March 2010. 

[](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/)This privacy policy has been published under a Creative Commons Sharealike license (http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/). This means that you are welcome to copy and adapt the license for your own use, as long as you publish the policy under the same license terms.

## Information collected from website visitors

When visiting a Kayako website, your activity, browser information and information about the referring site, along with an approximation of your location may be recorded. 

Kayako may publish this information in an aggregate, non-personally identifying way. 

We may also recorded this information linked to your IP address or e-mail address, if authenticated to the website. We will never publish this personally identifying information. 

Kayako uses this information to improve its websites, products and services and your experience with Kayako. We will not share this personally identifying information with a third party other than in the circumstances set out below. 

## Collection and use of personally identifying information

Kayako collects the e-mail addresses, names and potentially other information volunteered when you communicate with us. When you register with Kayako, we ask for information such as your name, organization information, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers and postal addresses. 

Kayako will use the information gathered for the provision of products and services to you; including billing, authentication, contact and improvement to said products services and its websites. 

Kayako's websites provide you with the facility to create and post content available, such as on our message boards or commenting sections. Any personally identifying information you publish using these facilities may be displayed publically. 

Kayako does not intentionally collect information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

### Credit card information

Your transaction may be processed by one of our third-party payment vendors: RBS WorldPay, 2Checkout, ICICI or Paymentech. These vendors are payment processors who can process your payment on behalf of Kayako. The vendor which will be used to process your own transaction will depend on the kind of product or subscription you purchase. 

### Protection of personally identifying information

Kayako may disclose personally identifying information to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations. This will only be done on a need-to-know basis. 

Kayako uses the services of third party vendors for storage, network and technical services. 

Personally identifying information may be transferred outside of your home country as part of our provision of services to you. 

When required by law (under governmental order, warrant or subpoena), or when Kayako believes that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights of Kayako or third parties, personally identifying information may be disclosed. 

Kayako reserves to right to publish correspondence and feedback sent to us in order to help us respond to the correspondence or to help other users. 

Kayako will take all reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access, use and alteration to personally identifying information. When passing personally identifying information to a third party, we will ensure that adequate protection of the information is applied by the recipient. 

Should Kayako be acquired or merged with another organization, your information may be transferred. We will notify you if your information is to be subject to a different privacy policy.

Should Kayako cease trading or file for bankruptcy, information held about you will not be transferred to a third party.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of information that our websites can store on your computer. Your computer provides this cookie when visiting the same website in the future. Cookies are used to enhance your experience with a website. 

Kayako uses cookies to identify visitors and track visits to our website, store login session information and to remember your user preferences. 

Visitors can disable the storage of cookies in their web browser, but should be aware that doing so may affect the quality of the experience with the website. In some cases, the website may not work at all. 

## Access to your information

You can change any of the personally identifying information volunteered to us by logging into the Kayako members' area: [https://members.kayako.net](https://members.kayako.net/). 

If you would like us to delete any personally identifying information held about you, we will do so on request unless we need to hold the information as part of the provision of products and services to you. 

## eTrust

You can contact eTrust regarding this privacy policy via their website: <http://www.etrust.org/about/privacy_contact.php>

## Contacting Kayako

You may contact Kayako using any of the methods outlined here: [www.kayako.com/company/contac/](http://www.kayako.com/company/contact/).

Our mailing addresses are:

Kayako Helpdesk Pvt. Ltd.  
Fourth Floor, Midland Financial Centre  
21-22 G.T.Road  
Jalandhar  
Punjab, 144001   
India

## Changes to this policy

From time to time we may make adjustments to this privacy policy. Changes to this policy will be made at Kayako's sole discretion. Kayako's users are encouraged to check this privacy policy for such changes. Your continued use of this site following changes to this privacy policy constitutes your acceptance of the changes.
